Finding Aid for Dorothy Leonard Judd Papers, 1935-1974
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Grand Rapids Politics and Reform
  - Citizens Action 1949-1955
    - Citizens Action origin (Box 7)
      (recall petitions ruled valid by court order)
    - Letters from citizens (pro and con) 1949 (Box 7)
    - All America City award 1949 (Box 7)
    - Communications with members (Box 7)
    - Dissolution of Citizens Action 1955 (Box 7)
    - Brochures and advertisements (Box 7)
    - Postcard poll on candidates 1949 (Box 7)
    - Finances (Box 7)
    - First election--February Primary 1950 (Box 7)
    - Politics and principles (Box 7)
    - CA News, 1950-1954 (Box 7)
    - February Primary 1952 (Box 7)
    - Primary and general elections 1953 (Box 7)
    - Elections 1954-1956 (Box 7)
    - Analysis of the political complexion of Grand Rapids 1944-1953 (Box 7)
    - Maps of GR wards with colored notations used for informational purposes during the 1950 election (Box 7)
      (separately cataloged and located)
    - Grand Rapids water system and pipe line bonds controversy, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Frank D. McKay Miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - Newspaper clippings concerning Grand Rapids politics 1949-1954, 4 expandable folders (Box 8)
      (largely from Frank McKay's Michigan Times and George Welsh's Shopping News)
    - Newspaper clippings concerning Grand Rapids politics 1949-1954, 1 folder; 1 expandable folder (Box 9)
  - George Welsh career
    - General information (Box 9)
    - GW as city manager 1929-1932 (Box 9)
      (opposition of Committee of 100)
    - Better Government League 1932-1934, 1951 (Box 9)
      (opposition to Welsh's replacement Ernest T. Conlon with information about his subsequent career)
    - GW as mayor 1938-1950 (Box 9)
    - GW activities 1952-1953 (Box 9)
    - GW as city manager 1954-1955 (Box 9)
    - Post-public office activities 1960-1974 (Box 9)
    - Postmortems (Box 9)
  - Grand Rapids Assessment Reform 1943-1973
    - Grand Rapids story in brief (Box 9)
    - Citizens tax studies 1943-1947 (Box 9)
    - Source materials used in assessment reform (Box 9)
    - Proposed single assessor amendment (Box 9)
    - Campaign for assessor amendment 1948-1949 (Box 9)
    - Assessor amendment wins (Box 9)
    - Clippings concerning the campaign 1948-1949 (Box 9)
    - Assessment reform at last 1950 (Box 9)
    - Assessment in Grand Rapids 1950-1953 (Box 9)
    - History of the 15 mill property tax limit (Box 9)
  - Sound recordings
    - Tape recording re 1952 campaign for mayor (Box 9)
    - Tape recording of speech by Dr. Henry Stob in support of May or Paul Goebel 1954 (Box 9)
    - Tape recording of Dorothy Judd reminiscences about Citizen Action (Box 9)